Encounters are mysterious! But the world is even more so!
لقاءات البشر مغلّفة بالغموض، والعالم تلفّه طبقات أكثر حتّى
I'm so glad I'm with you!
!أنا مسرورٌ حقّاً لكوني معك
Today is about two beautiful sisters!
!حلقة اليوم عن شقيقتين جميلتين
A case occurs behind dying words!
!تقع قضيّة وراء رسالة احتضار
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ دماغه لبالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
"The Sealed Bathroom Murder Case (Part 1)."
جريمة قتل الحمّام المغلق (الجزء الأوّل)
I'm home!
!رجعت
Where were you? That took a long time.
ما الذي كنتِ تفعلينه؟ تأخّرتِ
I got stuck at the convenience store.
أطلت في متجر التموينات
Aoshima Mina (24) Haido Dept. Store Clerk
(آوشيما مينا (24 محاسبة في مركز تسوّق هايدو
I made sure to buy everything you asked for, Sis!
اشتريتُ كلّ الأشياء التي طلبتِها منّي يا أختي
Bath detergents, tape, and beer!
مطهّر حوض الاستحمام وشريط لاصق وجعّة
Thanks, I forgot to buy bath detergent,
(26) آوشيما ماسايو موظّفة في مصرف بيكا
Aoshima Masayo (26) Beika Bank Employee
آسفة، نشيت شراء مطهّر حوض الاستحمام
and the convenience store by my apartment is being remodeled.
ومتجر التموينات بقرب شقّتي قيد التجديد
But are you really taking the video tape with that idol show on it?
لكن هل ستأخذينها معكِ حقّاً؟ أشرطة الفيديو لبرنامج الفنّانات الذي كنتِ تسجّلينه
Don't be like that. I moved out of here for your sake.
تعايشي مع ذلك، فقد انتقلتُ من هنا لأجلك
That seems like a lot of work. Can I help?
يبدو أنّ هذا يتطلّب جهداً، هل أساعدك؟
Could you cut some strips of tape and stick them along the table?
هلّا قصصتِ الشريط اللاصق لأجزاء بطول ملائم ورتّبتِها على طرف الطاولة إذاً؟
Sorry for suddenly coming over like this
أعتذر على القدوم فجأةً هكذا
and having you go shopping and help me pack.
وجعلك تساعديني بالتسوّق وحزم الأمتعة
Don't be silly. It's no problem.
ما الذي تقولينه؟ هذا لا يُستحقّ الذكر
Oh, right! I forgot!
!صحيح، نسيت
Before we pack...
...قبل أن نحزم
...we have to make a toast to my happiness-filled little sister!
علينا شرب نخب لأختي الصغيرة !الممتلئة سعادةً
Oh, we don't have to do that!
لا داعي لتفعلي ذلك
No, no!
!كلا، كلا
I've been so busy since you announced you were getting married
فقد كنتُ مشغولةً مُذ حُدّد زواجكما
that I haven't gotten to celebrate it properly!
فلم أحتفل كما يجب، أليس كذلك؟
So this is your sister's meager little celebration!
لذا هذا أبسط ما يمكن أن تفعله أختك للاحتفال
Please accept it.
فلتقبليه رجاءً
Your beauty is a crime!
جمالك جريمةٌ بحدّ ذاته
Have a look at these roses I've brought for you!
أمعني النظر في هذه الورود التي سأهديك إيّاها
They're all bright red after being enamored by you!
!كلّها واقعة تحت تأثيرك، ومصبوغة بأحمر فاقع
Get it?!
!أو ما شابه
I think that stupid look is more of a crime.
أرى أنّ النظرة الحمقاء على وجهه هي الأقرب للجريمة
Yes.
أجل
I guess kids can't understand stylish, grownup lines like that!
لا يفهم الأطفال كلام البالغين !المنمّق هذا، صحيح؟
Yeah, real stylish...
...كلام منمّق
He seems to be in a good mood...
يبدو العمّ في مزاجٍ حسن
Yeah! Because Okino Yoko-chan is having a concert tonight!
أجل، فهنالك حفلة الليلة لأوكينو يوكو-تشان
Shouldn't we go, Dad? It'll be really crowded if we don't go soon!
أليس علينا الذهاب يا أبي؟ إذا لم ندخل في الصفّ سريعاً، ستكتظّ القاعة
Don't worry!
لا داعي للقلق
If we show them the autographed tickets Yoko-chan gave us,
إذا أرينا موظّف التذاكر هذه التذاكر الموقّعة ،التي أعطتنا إيّاها يوكو-تشان
they'll let us go in the back--
...فسنستطيع الدخول من الباب الخلفـ
Huh?
ماذا؟
What's wrong, Dad?!
!ما الخطب يا أبي؟
There's a hole here!
!يوجد ثقب
Don't tell me you dropped your ticket?!
!أيمكن أنّك أسقطتها؟
Not there! Not there! Not there! Where did my Yoko-chan go?!
!ليست هنا! ليست هنا! ليست هنا
What about the bathroom? You ran in there right when we got here.
أليست في دورة المياه؟ فقد دخلتها فور وصولك هنا
The bathroom! The bathroom!
دورة المياه! دورة المياه! لا بدّ !أنّها هناك! دورة المياه
Well? Did you find it?
إذاً؟ هل وجدتها؟
Nope. Zilch.
كلا
Don't worry! I'm sure they'll let us in if we explain the situation!
لا تقلق، أنا متأكّدة أنّهم سيدخلوننا إذا شرحنا الوضع
Don't be dumb!
!يا حمقاء
I can't let myself look stupid when I give her a bouquet!
كيف أستطيع جعل نفسي أبدو بذاك !المنظر الساذج وأنا أحمل باقة ورود؟
Wait.
لحظة
As I recall, you have midterms next week, right?
وفقما أذكر، فقد قلتِ أنّ لديكِ اختبارات نصفيّة الأسبوع القادم، صحيح؟
Yeah.
أجل
Then give me your ticket so you can go home and study!
!فلتعطني تذكرتكِ إذاً، وارجعي للبيت وادرسي
Forget it!
!كلا
I know! Let's say it was actually...
..وجدتُها! لنقل أنّ من أسقط التذكرة
Come on, Dad.
مهلك، أبي
Yes, yes! Let's say that Conan dropped his ticket and--
أجل، أجل، لنقل أنّ كونان كان ...من أسقط التذكرة
Knock that off!
!يكفي هذا
I'm sorry!
!آسف
What do you mean you can't come, Kenji?!
ما قصدك بأنّك لن تستطيع !القدوم يا كينجي؟
A cold?! You'll get over it at the concert!
!زكام؟! سيزول إذا شاهدت الحفلة
Do you know how hard it was
أنت تعرف كم عانيت
getting tickets to Okino Yoko's concert?!
لأجل الحصول على تذاكر !حفلة لأوكينو يوكو
Just get over here! My sister and I planned on taking your car there!
تعال فوراً بأيّ حال! فقد اتّفقت مع أختي !بأن نذهب للقاعة بسيّارتك
Eh?! You can't?! Wait, Kenji!
ماذا؟ لا تستطيع؟
Kenji?!
كينجي؟
Urgh! You useless jerk!
!يا إلهي، عديم الفائدة هذا
Umm...
...المعذرة
Yes?!
أجل؟
Do you have an extra ticket for Okino Yoko-chan's concert tonight?
ألديكِ تذكرة إضافيّة لحفلة الليلة؟
Y-Yes...
...أ-أجل
In that case, might you let me have it for a small sum?
في تلك الحالة، أيمكنك بيعها لي بثمنٍ منخفض؟
Hold on, Dad! That's a waste! They'll let you in if you just explain!
!لحظة يا أبي
Quiet! A man's pride can't be exchanged for money!
اخرسي! لا يمكن مقايضة !فخر الرجل بالمال
You're so vain...
...يا لتفاخرك
Mister!
!يا عمّ
You didn't lose your ticket in the car, either.
لم تسقط تذكرتك في السيّارة أيضاً
O-Oh.
فـ-فهمت
So, would you be willing to sell it to me?
إذاً، بكم ستبيعينها لي؟
No, no, you appear troubled, so you can have it for free.
لا، لا، تبدو في مشكلة فسأمنحك إيّاها بالمجّان
For free?
بالمجّان؟
For f-free?! Really?!
بالمجّان؟! حقّاً؟
Yes! In exchange, could I ask one favor of you?
أجل، لكن بالمقابل، أيمكنني طلب معروف واحد منك؟
Yes! Anything at all!
!أجل! أيّ شيء
What's with him?
ما خطب العمّ؟
I thought he was acting on a man's pride, but I guess it didn't matter.
ظننتُ أنّ فخره الرجوليّ كان يحكم سلوكه، لكن يبدو أنّ الأمر لم يهم
I'm sorry to ask you to do this.
أعتذر على طلبي هذا
No, it's no problem! We're just going to pick up your sister!
البتّة، سنذهب لاصطحاب شقيقتك معنا بالسيّارة لا أكثر
Good thing you rented this car, huh?
!من الحسن أنّنا استأجرنا سيّارة
Yeah! It's lucky I had to take a trip for work this morning!
أجل، كان لديّ عمل في مكان بعيد هذا الصباح، فحالفنا الحظّ
But what could've gotten into them?
لكن ما خطب مينا يا ترى؟
They couldn't wait for tonight's concert, but then didn't show up.
،كانت تتطلّع لحفلة الليلة كثيراً لكن لم تأتي لمكاننا المتّفق حتّى
Did you try calling her?
أجرّبتِ الاتّصال بها؟
Yes... but she won't answer. And the answering machine isn't on.
أجل، لكنّها لم تجب
I just hope nothing strange has happened...
آمل أنّ أمراً غريباً لم يحصل لها
Strange?
أمر غريب؟
My sister's been acting strange lately.
كانت أختي غريبة نوعاً ما مؤخراً
She's been depressed ever since announcing she was getting married.
تشعر بإحباط مُذ حُدّد زواجها
Sometimes she'll cry for no reason.
وتبكي أحياناً بلا سبب
That's why I invited her to tonight's concert! To cheer her up!
لذا دعوتها لحفلة الليلة للترويح عن نفسها
Say, it's had me curious this whole time.
...بالمناسبة، كنتُ أتساءل لفترة
That bandana around your head... is it...?
...أيمكن أنّ العصابة على رأسك
that came with Yoko-chan's album that was released yesterday!
مع الإصدار الأوّل الخاص لألبوم يوكو-تشان الذي صدر بالأمس
So it was Yoko-chan's!
!كانت يوكو-تشان بالفعل إذاً
It's amazing you can get things like that!
...من المذهل حصولك على شيءٍ كهذا
You're so lucky!
!يا لحظّك
Eh? You're fans, but you haven't bought it?!
ماذا؟ أنتم معجبون، لكن لم تشتروه؟
It comes with a key holder, too!
!تأتي معها حاملة مفاتيح أيضاً
She gives us all her CDs in person, so we don't get extras...
،تعطينا أقراصها كلّها بنفسها فلا نحصل على إضافات
Eh?! In person?! You know Yoko-chan?!
!ماذا؟! بنفسها؟! تعرفون يوكو-تشان؟
Yes, we kinda met during a case...
أجل، التقينا في قضيّةٍ ما
C-Case?
قـ-قضيّة؟
Yeah, my name is Mori Kogoro. I'm a detective.
أجل، فاسمي موري كوغورو وأعمل متحرّياً
Is something the matter?
أهنالك خطبٌ ما؟
N-No! I just recognized that name! You're so famous that I...
!لا، أعرف اسمك فحسب ...أنت شخصيّة ذائعة الصيت، لذا
No, I'm not that famous!
لا، ليس بذاك الحدّ
Your little sister lives here alone?
أتعيش أختك الصغيرة هنا بمفردها؟
No, I lived here with her until just last week.
كلّا، كنّا نعيش سويّاً حتّى الأسبوع الفائت
I moved out so her fiancé can move in with her next month.
ستعيش مع خطيبها هنا ابتداءً من الشهر القادم، فانتقلت
Her shoes are here.
يبدو أنّ حذاءها هنا
She must still be asleep.
لا بدّ أنّها لا تزال نائمة
I'll go get her. You can relax in the living room.
،سأذهب لاستدعائها إذاً يمكنكم الاسترخاء في غرفة المعيشة
We'll only be a minute!
!لن أطيل
R-Right...
...حـ-حسناً
Come on, now. It'll take an hour to get there!
مهلكم، تبقّت ساعة على فتح القاعة
Now, now! Don't be in such a rush!
هوّن عليك، لا داعي للعجلة
The room is filled with idol posters!
!الغرفة مليئة بملصقات الفنّانين
Yoko-chan, Anzai Asuka, Two-Mix, Hoshino Terumi...
يوكو-تشان وأنزاي أسوكا ...وتو-ميكس وهوشينو تيرومي
Amazing! They even have Lex, and they disbanded!
!مذهل! توجد ليكس قبل انفصالها حتّى
It's also amazing you know so much about this stuff...
أنت المذهل بمعرفتك لهذا القدر منهم
Masayo-san certainly loves idols!
يبدو أنّ ماسايو-سان تحبّ الفنّانين حقّاً
Her sister must've had it rough, putting up with this.
لا بدّ أنّ أختها عانت بالعيش معها
I think they both like idols.
يبدو أنّهما كانتا معجبتين الاثنتين
See? There are two of everything, even photo books and CDs!
انظر، توجد نسختان من كلّ شيء حتّى الكتب المصوّرة والأقراص المدمجة
And they have their names on them.
كما عليها اسماهما
But why didn't Masayo-san take them when she moved?
لكن لمَ لم تأخذها ماسايو-سان معها عندما انتقلت؟
There's probably so much that she couldn't take it all at once.
لا بدّ أنّ العدد كبيرٌ جدّاً فلم تستطع حملها سويّاً
See? Look at all these moving boxes.
انظري، لا يزال يوجد هذا العدد من صناديق الانتقال
Still...
...لكن
W-What's that?!
ما-ما هذا؟
Mina! Mina!
!مينا! مينا
Mister!
!يا عمّ
Yeah!
أجل
I know you're in there!
!أعرف أنّك هنا
What's wrong?!
!أهناك خطبٌ ما؟
Mina!
هنا
'Goodbye' [written reversed]
"وداعاً"
Mina! Mina!
!مينا! مينا
W-What's that?!
...هـ-هذا
Don't tell me it's locked from the inside?!
!أيمكن أنّها مقفلة من الداخل؟
No, there's no lock on this door!
كلا، لا قفل على هذا الباب
I think it's been taped shut from the inside!
!يبدو أنّه مغلق بشريط لاصق من الداخل
Alright! Let's all bust it open!
!حسناً! لندفعه جميعاً
Ready, go!
...استعداد
Mina...
...مينا
S-Suicide?
ا-انتحار؟
Ran! The police! Call the police!
!ران! الشرطة! اتّصلي بالشرطة
Right!
!حسناً
M-My sister... Will she live?!
أ-أختي... أيمكن إنقاذها؟
I'm sorry, but she's gone...
...للأسف، توقّف تنفسها
This can't be happening!
!لا يمكن
The door and the window were both taped shut!
باب الحمّام والنافذة موصدان بالشريط اللاصق
And on the floor are two open bottles of different bath detergents!
وعلى الأرض علبتيّ مطهّر حوض استحمام مفتوحتين مختلفتيّ الصنف
Maybe it was a suicide?
أهو انتحار حقّاً؟
But the cuts on her wrists bother me!
...لكنّها تحيّرني، آثار القطع هذه على معصمها
No, it's not! This wasn't a suicide! It was a murder!
!كلا، ليس صحيحاً
But if that's the case, I don't get how it was done...
...لكن لا أفهم، كيف استطاع
How did the killer leave the room?!
كيف استطاع القاتل مغادرة الحمّام؟
How could someone leave this completely sealed space?!
مغادرة هذا الحيّز الموصد بالشريط اللاصق؟
The deceased is Aoshima Mina-san, age 24.
المُتوفاة هي آوشيما مينا-سان، 24 عاماً
The cause of death was blood loss stemming from the severance
كان سبب الوفاة هو فقدان الدم الناتج من قطع
of her ulnar artery caused by cuts to her left wrist.
الشريان الزنديّ على معصمها الأيسر
And it was you, her sister, who found her, Masayo-san?
،ومن اكتشفت جثّتها كانت أختها أنت يا ماسايو-سان، صحيح؟
Y-Yes.
أ-أجل
And, at the scene just by coincidence yet again...
...ومن صادف وجوده هنا مُجدداً، كالمعتاد
...was I, Mori Kogoro!
!أنا، موري كوغورو
Inspector Megure.
حضرة المفتّش ميغوري
The truth is, Masayo-san had asked me to pick Mina-san up in my car.
في الواقع، طلبت منّي ماسايو-سان القدوم لاصطحاب مينا-سان بالسيّارة
We went into the bathroom when we noticed something was strange.
لاحظنا أمراً غريباً في غرفة حوض الاستحمام، فدخلنا
By which you mean the tape on this window and door?
بالغريب، تقصد هذا الشريط اللاصق على الباب والنافذة، صحيح؟
Yes... there was tape all over the inside, so the room was sealed off.
أجل، كان المكان موصداً بعناية بالشريط اللاصق من الداخل، فكانت غرفة مغلقة
There's no doubt it was a suicide, though.
لا شكّ بأنّه انتحار
Still, why would someone slitting their wrist to commit suicide
لكن، لمَ يُقدم شخص على وشك قطع معصمه والانتحار
need to seal off this room?
بإغلاق المكان بإحكام هكذا؟
It's probably because mixing chlorine and acid-based detergents
لا بدّ أنّ السبب هو صدور غاز كلوريّ سام
produces a poisonous chlorine gas.
عند خلط مطهّر كلور ومطّهر حمضي
She sealed the room so the gas wouldn't leak out.
فأحكمت إغلاق المكان كيلا يتسرّب الغاز
But Mori-kun. These are both chlorine-based.
لكن يا موري-كن، كلاهما كلوريّان
Besides, chlorine gas isn't bad enough to seal the room...
كما أنّ غاز الكلور ليس بتلك الخطورة بحيث تحكم إغلاق الحجرة
Inspector... the late Mina-san wasn't a pro like us.
حضرة المفتّش، لم تكن مينا-سان المتوفّاة محترفة مثلنا
She wouldn't have known the strength of chlorine gas.
لا بدّ أنّها كانت تجهل قوّة غاز الكلور
Even so...
...مع ذلك
I also believe she was in a very confused state before killing herself!
كما أنّي أعتقد أنّ مينا-سان كانت !في حالة ارتباك قبل إقدامها على الانتحار
In short, this is what happened.
أي هذا ما حصل
To commit suicide, she prepared two types of bathroom detergent
حضّرت صنفي مطهّر حوض استحمام للانتحار
and sealed off this room.
وأغلقت حجرة حوض الاستحمام هذه
But when she tried to produce the gas,
لكن عندما حاولت إطلاق الغاز، أدركت أنّها
she realized she had bought the wrong detergents.
أخطأت في اختيار المطهّر
With no other choice, she cut her wrist with a razor in the room
لم يكن لديها خيارٌ آخر، فقطعت معصمها بالشفرة عند الحوض
and left the cuts in the warm water to kill herself.
وتركت جرحها في ماءٍ دافئ حتّى لا يتوقّف النزيف
Inspector, take a look at this.
حضرة المفتّش، انظر لهذا
I found this receipt in the living room.
وجدتُ هذا الإيصال في غرفة المعيشة
Mina-san purchased two bath detergents and tape
اشترت مينا-سان مطهريّ الحوض والشريط اللاصق
at a convenience store last night.
من متجر التموينات البارحة
It's proof she decided to commit suicide and prepared hastily.
إنّه دليلٌ على تحضيرها في عجلة من أمرها بعدما قرّرت الانتحار
Hey! Takagi-kun!
!تاكاغي-كن، تعال
Yes, sir?
أجل
Go confirm this at the convenience store.
اذهب لمتجر التموينات وتحقّق من هذا
Understood!
حاضر
The roll of tape was found at the bottom of the bath,
وجدنا لفافة الشريط اللاصق أسفل الحوض
so this situation is plausible if Mina-san was acting hastily...
لذا فالوضع معقول إذا كانت مينا-سان تتصرّف بعجالة
But she hurried too much!
لكنّها تعجّلت كثيراً
C-Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
This lady's wrist is cut in rushed zig-zags!
الآثار على معصم هذه الآنسة هي لخطوط متعرّجة شُكّلت بعجلة
S-So it is!
!بـ-بالفعل
Most hesitant cuts made by people committing suicide are parallel.
في العادة، تكون الآثار من تردّد الشخص المُقدم على الانتحار موازيةً للجرح القاتل
They almost never crisscross like this.
من الغريب أن تتداخل بهذا الشكل
If I didn't know better, I'd say--
...أيمكن أنّه
It just happened that way.
مجرّد مصادفة
It just shows how confused she was at the time.
هذا يُظهر حالة الارتباك التي كانت فيها
Oh, geez...
...أنت
But would someone like her clean up?
لكن هل سيقوم شخص مثلها بالتنظيف؟
Clean up?
التنظيف؟
See? Look at this blood! It suddenly stops at the edge!
انظروا لهذا الدمّ، إنّه متوقّف بانتظام عند الطرف
That means she cleaned up the blood after it went flying, right?
هذا يعني أنّها مسحته بعدما تطاير الدم، أليس كذلك؟
You're so stupid! Nobody committing suicide would do that!
أحمق! لن يقوم شخص مُقدم !على الانتحار بذلك
Then why does it suddenly stop?
لمَ توقّف الأثر فجأةً إذاً؟
Well... Because...
...السبب... حسناً
When the blood sprayed, there was something here, or...
...عندما تطاير الدم، كان يوجد شيءٌ هنا، أو
Or someone was next to her when she cut her wrist.
كان أحدٌ بجوارها عندما قطعت معصمها
Right?
أليس كذلك؟
Inspector, if I didn't know better, I'd say...
...حضرة المفتّش، أيمكن أنّ هذا
Yes, it may've been a murder.
أجل، قد تكون جريمة قتل
Could it have been the tape?
ربما كان الشريط اللاصق
The tape was at the bottom of the bathtub, right?
فقد كانت اللفافة في أسفل الحوض، أليس كذلك؟
Ah! If the tape was on the edge of the tub
صحيح! إذا كانت اللفافة على طرف الحوض
and it fell when she cut her wrist...
...وسقطت عندما قطعت معصمها
...it would all fit!
!ستكتمل الصورة
Thank you! You've helped solve the mystery!
!شكراً لك
It was nothing...
...لا
Inspector Megure.
مفتّش ميغوري
It appears only Mina-san's fingerprints are on the tape.
يبدو أنّ البصمات على الشريط اللاصق هي لمينا-سان فحسب
Prints from both index fingers and thumbs show up clearly.
آثار سبّابتها ومعصمها تظهر بوضوح على الشرائط
I see.
فهمت
So we can probably assume this "Goodbye" was her dying message.
مما يعني أنّنا نستطيع افتراض أنّ "وداعاً" هذه بمثابة وصيّتها
Meaning it was a suicide...
لعلّه كان انتحاراً بالفعل
Of course it was. This bathroom was completely sealed off!
بالطبع، فقد كان هذا الحمّام مغلقاً بالكامل
Oh no! I completely forgot!
!كلا
F-Forgot what, Mori-kun?!
نـ-نسيت ماذا يا موري-كن؟
Masayo-san.
ماسايو-سان
Y-Yes?!
أجل
As I recall, you said this then...
...وفقما أذكر، فقد قلتِ آنذاك
"Then"?
آ-آنذاك؟
You said I could have a ticket to Okino Yoko-chan's concert tonight!
!ستعطينني تذكرة لحفلة يوكو-تشان الليلة
Huh?
ماذا؟
Stop that, Dad! This isn't the time...
مهلك، أبي! هذا ليس وقتاً مناسباً
Come on! We can at least catch the finale if we go now!
أين المشكلة؟ يمكننا مشاهدة ختام الحفلة على الأقل إذا ذهبنا الآن
I'll go get it. I think my sister put them all in the living room.
سأذهب لجلبها إذاً، أظنّ أختي تركتها في غرفة المعيشة
Thanks!
!شكراً لك
Say.
أخبريني
These boxes have bend marks. Did you put them together before?
بهذه الصناديق آثار ثني، هل فتحتِها قبلاً؟
Y-Yes! I had so many things to take that I decided to get them later!
أ-أجل، فقد كانت لديّ أمتعة كثيرة ...فقرّت تأجيلها
Oh! So that's why you had your sister help you then?
فهمت، لذا طلبتِ من أختك مساعدتك وقتها؟
After all, the edges of that table are all sticky!
فكلّ أطراف تلك الطاولة دبقة
It got left behind by pieces of tape, right?
تعني أنّ شريطاً لاصقاً كان ملصقاً عليها، أليس كذلك؟
Having someone line up pieces of tape makes packing a cinch, huh?
جعل أحدهم يقطع الشريط اللاصق لأجزاء يجعل حزم الأمتعة سهلاً، صحيح؟
Conan-kun! Where are you?
كونان-كن، أين أنت؟
That damn kid. Every single time!
يا إلهي، ذاك الصبيّ الشقيّ... كلّ مرّة
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
L-Little boy! Your sister is calling you!
!يا-يا فتى، أختك تناديك
You're right! I better go!
معكِ حقّ، عليّ الذهاب
There's no point wiping away the tape marks.
لا فائدة من محي آثار الشريط اللاصق
The examiner touched them and photographed them after I told him.
فقد لمسها المُحلّل قبل قليل والتقط صوراً عندما أخبرته
Here you are!
!كنتَ هنا
I'm sorry for the trouble!
أعتذر على الإزعاج
Bye-bye, lady!
!مع السلامة يا آنسة
Bye-bye!
مع السلامة
Oh, Conan-kun! You know not to scamper around!
!كونان-كن، تعرف أنّه لا يصحّ بك التجوّل
There's no question about it.
لا شكّ في الأمر
Conan!
!كونان
Yes. Mina-san's killer was Masayo-san!
!أجل، المجرم الذي قتل مينا-سان هي ماسايو-سان
Goodbye
لكن لا أفهم
is how she escaped the room sealed with tape!
كيف هربت من الحجرة المغلقة بالشريط اللاصق؟
And what's this strange feeling that's been bugging me?
وما ذاك الشعور الغريب العالق في رأسي لفترة؟
Hey! What's that?!
انظر، ما ذاك؟
Yes. Mina-san didn't commit suicide. She was murdered.
أجل، لم تنتحر مينا-سان، بل قُتلت
By you, Masayo-san! Her older sister!
!بأيدي أختها، أنت يا ماسايو-سان
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
"The Sealed Bathroom Murder Case (Part 2)."
جريمة قتل الحمّام المغلق (الجزء الثاني)
Next Conan's hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Bandanna.
عصابة رأس
Next episode is part two.
!الحلقة القادمة هي الجزء الثاني
The culprit is the fiance.
!أنت القاتل أيّها الخطيب
No, it's Masayo-san.
كلا، كان ماسايو-سان